const dummyTest = {
  id: 'test1',
  date: 'Wed Jan 06 2021 20:14:43 GMT+0500 (Pakistan Standard Time)',
  data: [
    { question: "What's your current study status?", answer: 'Matric' },
    {
      question:
        'From following, which bachelors degree program, you want to go?',
      answer: 'BS(CS)'
    },
    { question: "What's your favourite subjects?", answer: 'asdsa' },
    { question: 'Current Status', answer: '&Student' },
    { question: 'Desired Profession', answer: 'asdsa' },
    { question: 'What game do you like the most?', answer: '&Indoor games' },
    {
      question: 'what kind of hobbies do you have?',
      answer: '&Travel, meet strangers'
    },
    {
      question: 'Please choose the word that describes you most of the time.',
      answer: 'Structured'
    },
    {
      question: 'Please choose the word that describes you most of the time.',
      answer: 'Feeling'
    },
    {
      question: 'Are you a person that is more inclined to',
      answer: 'Be in Control'
    },
    {
      question: 'In general, would you describe yourself as more',
      answer: 'Appreciative'
    },
    {
      question: 'Do your coworkers/Fellows consider you to be more',
      answer: 'Outgoing'
    },
    {
      question: 'Do you consider yourself a person that likes to focus on',
      answer: 'What is'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which role is more natural for you at work',
      answer: 'To critique and analyze'
    },
    {
      question:
        'At work you are part of a planning committee. Are you more inspired by',
      answer: 'Vision'
    },
    { question: 'What is more satisfying at work', answer: 'Organizing' }
  ]
};

export default dummyTest;
